If it is good to give thanks to the
Lord,
then it is not good [laughter]
to not give thanks to the Lord. What's
our theme for this day's star worship
experience? Todah.
And [clears throat] todah means thank
you. Let's read from Psalm 92 and verse
1 New Living Translation. All of us are
going to read it together. Psalm 92
verse 1 New Living Translation.
Let's go.
It is good to give thanks to the Lord to
sing praises to the Most High.
If it is good to give thanks to the
Lord,
then it is not good to not give thanks
to the Lord. A new way
is study on the neuroscience of
gratitude and its effect on the brain
established the fact that gratitude
literally rewires the human brain.
I mean, they put brains under scanners
and watched what happens to the brains
as people gave thanks.
And they said,
"Gratitude literally restructures
the human brain." That's really, really
powerful.
They said, "Gratitude increases the gray
matter in the brain and strengthens the
neural pathways that are responsible for
empathy."
Isn't that powerful? Your capacity for
love increases. The pathways that are
responsible for perception,
for learning,
and for emotional regulation. Isn't that
amazing? In other words, you will be
smarter.
You will be more intelligent. You will
have You will be more creative. You will
have access to divine ideas when you go
on the channel of gratitude.
Woo!
That's exciting for me.
And you are able to,
you know, experience better self-control
when you practice gratitude.
The American Brain Foundation says that
gratitude releases
dopamine and serotonin,
the hormones that improve our mood and
act as antidepressants.
Wow.
Yes.
The feeling of joy, the feeling of
pleasure, they are controlled by those
chemicals in the brain,
dopamine and serotonin.
And the Bible says, sorry.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm used to that.
Scientific research has proved that your
brain secretes those hormones when you
are in gratitude mode. I'm describing
what is going on right now. Oh, thank
you, Jesus.
Thank you, Jesus.
Uh
Add this to that this experience.
The heavens are opened.
Somebody's brain is opening up.
Something is shifting in someone's
brain.
Your access to creative ideas is
shifting to a new level right now. If
you believe that, say a powerful amen.
So, isn't it amazing that science is
agreeing with what the Bible said
thousands of years ago?
It is a good thing to give thanks to the
Lord and to sing praises to your name, O
Most High. First Thessalonians 5:18, the
Apostle Paul said,
"In all things, give thanks, for this is
the will of God in Christ Jesus
concerning you."
Gratitude, in short, puts you on God's
frequency.
And when you get on God's frequency,
miracles happen.
Woo!
John chapter 6, Jesus faced a huge crowd
that needed food. And he asked, "What do
you have around here?" They said, "Five
loaves of bread and two fish." He said,
"Bring them."
And John chapter 6 verse 11, New Living
Translation,
"Then Jesus took the loaves, gave thanks
to God, and distributed them to the
people. Afterward, he did the same with
the fish, and they all ate as much as
they wanted." Wow.
Gratitude. Jesus got on the gratitude
frequency, and the gratitude frequency
was the miracle frequency. Thank you,
Jesus. As you get on the gratitude
frequency today, lack is destroyed.
Miracles of multiplication,
provision.
Bad news before you came today has
turned into good news.
Sicknesses and diseases drop out of
people's bodies here, now.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Mhm.
So, gratitude has value. That's why we
talk about Thanksgiving.
You can't give something to if it does
not have value. Am I right? Yeah.
Thanksgiving. It has value. And what did
God say? What did Jesus say in Luke
6:38?
New King James version, "Give, and it
shall be given unto you. Good measure,
pressed down, shaken together, running
over, shall men give to your bosom." So,
you give God gratitude, you give him
thanks,
he gives to you good measure, pressed
down, shaken together, running over.
Your life is changing right now in this
service.
Sorry.
It's not you. My life is changing right
here in this service. Anyway, finally,
the research on gratitude said that
it is gratitude for specific things
that shifts the brain. Not just general
gratitude. Lord, I'm grateful. I just
thank you for everything. That doesn't
work.
Lord, I thank you for making me a mother
of many nations. Lord, I thank for my
husband. And you describe the husband.
Hallelujah. Remember, this gratitude is
the language of faith. Are you ready?
Because we're going to do it now.
Right before the tomb of Lazarus, Jesus
shouted, "John 11:41 and 42, Father, I
thank you specific because you hear me
always. And I say this so that the
people will believe that you are the one
that sent me. Are you ready? Jump to
your feet with me. Let's do it. Let's do
it. Action. Let's do it. Hallelujah.
Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. Thank
you, Lord. Will you go ahead
giving thanks.
Thank him as if the miracle has already
happened.
That's important. No, no, no, no. Don't
position yourself like something is
going to happen or the
or like a victim. No, no, no, no, no.
Lord, I thank you
for my car. Lord, I thank you
for helping me to win souls. 10 souls
this month. Lord, I thank you
for making me a blessing to my
generation. Lord, I thank you for my
factory.
>> [laughter]
>> Hallelujah. Lord, I thank you for this
particular approval. Lord, I thank you.
Lord, I thank you for my healing. I
thank you for my miracle. Lord, I thank
you that I'm healthy. Lord, I thank you
that I I'm sickness free. Lord, I thank
you. Hallelujah. Hallelujah. Hallelujah.
Hallelujah. Hallelujah. Lord Jesus,
thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you.
In Jesus' name we pray.
Heavenly Father,
we came here today
to thank you.
To thank you because your goodness is
immeasurable. Your love for us is
immeasurable. And your wisdom is
immeasurable. Your power is
immeasurable. And we know right now is
the moment of power.
And I stand by the authority in the name
of Jesus Christ to declare
in this service
there's resurrection.
The way Lazarus came out of that grave
I speak to everything that has been
lost, everything Satan stole, everything
that has been going wrong.
Come out.
>> [laughter]
>> I prophesy in Jesus' name restoration of
health.
The power of sickness is destroyed in
this service. The power of luck
destroyed in this service.
Cycle of failure destroyed in this
service.
I declare in Jesus' name restoration,
healing,
deliverance,
possession,
taking over new territories,
supernatural promotion,
change of status,
change of name.
And I declare so.
And it happens now. Someone gets a new
baby.
Someone gets a husband. Someone gets a
wife. Yes, somebody's job has just
changed. Somebody's position and title
just changed.
Hallelujah. Where you were yesterday,
everybody knew you were there. I declare
your relocation to a new level, a new
dimension. Thank you, heavenly Father.
Will you go ahead and give him thanks
one more time? Give him thanks one more
time. Give him thanks.
We're grateful, Lord.
In Jesus' name we have prayed.
Just before we conclude this prayer,
is your life okay with God? Do you have
a relationship with God? Sin is man's
greatest problem and that's why he sent
Jesus to die for us on the cross.
Jesus already died, already took all our
pains, all our sicknesses. and all God
wants for us is to accept Jesus already
paid the price and to accept his
forgiveness. He's already there. He's
giving it.
If you are that honest person who says
my relationship with God is not okay, I
cannot say that I'm a child of God. Can
you please put your hand on your heart
where you are? You may be present at our
physical service, you may be home, or
anywhere, you may be online. Can you put
your hand on your heart
and say this prayer after me?
Now, can you remain standing if you are
present in our services? Every other
person can be seated. And can you say
this prayer after me? Dear God,
I believe that Jesus paid for my sins. I
ask you to forgive me and to accept me
as your child.
Thank you for hearing my prayer
in Jesus' name.
Let me pray for you.
Heavenly Father, we are all excited
about our brothers and sisters
who have received forgiveness today. We
know what has happened as your word
promised. Jesus said there is joy in
heaven among the angels when this
happens. We know also the nature of sin
is removed from them and you have put
your own nature in them to give them
capacity to live like you. So, we say
thank you and we just ask, Father, teach
them to know you personally.
Teach them to love you
and to love other people the rest of
their lives
in Jesus' name.
Daystar raising role models.